#### **EDUN OLUKUNLE ELIJAH**

I am a self-motivated and goal-oriented developer with experience building websites and web applications. I am adept at coming up with real solutions to satisfy client requirements. I have experience working with ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET Core REST API, Entity Framework Core, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgresSQL, Git, GitHub, and Git-Action, Docker, Kubernetes.

House no 18, Kadiri Street, Alausa, Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria, NG. +2348169688127
Email:kunle\_edun@yahoo.com
Github:https://github.com/gktech1
Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/edunolukunle-7a9468120/

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Decagon, Lagos — Software Engineer

AUGUST 2020 - Present

- A member of a team developing and implementing backend APIs for a Water distribution Application.
- Built projects with .Net, React.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres, or NoSQL databases like MongoDB.
- Experience writing unit and integration test.
- Practice Agile methodologies.

## Earlycode, Abuja — software developer

SEPTEMBER 2018-2020

- A member of a team that developed a web based ecommerce solution.
- Experience writing unit test.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres

# New Horizon, Lagos — software developer

SEPTEMBER 2018-2022

- A member of a team that developed a web based ecommerce solution.
- Experience writing unit test.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- React Hooks
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- SQLServer
- MySQL
- Postgresql
- Heroku
- Jira
- .Net mvc
- .Net web Api
- Docker
- Version Control with Git and Github.
- Test-Driven Development.

### **PROJECTS**

# Wema Bank Customer Onboarding Application:

This project is a microservice web application for registration and login of customer to onboard them and perform necessary trasaction that is needed to be done in bank.

Technologies Used - C#, MySql, Docker.

Link: https://github.com/Gktech1/WemaBank-CustomerOnboarding

# AquaWaterPlc API:

The project Is a water distribution project, we are tasked to build an application that facilitates water distribution.

**Technologies Used:** .Net WebApi, Swagger, heroku, Postgres. **Link:** <a href="https://aquawaterapp.herokuapp.com/swagger/index.html">https://aquawaterapp.herokuapp.com/swagger/index.html</a>

### Contact API

This project is a contact api application to manage contacts information using C-sharp, API ASP.NET Core Framework, Swagger, Heroku. **Technologies Used:** .Net WebApi, Swagger

Link: https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

# **Bank Application:**

This project is a window form application with login and registration, account opening, deposit, withdrawal, transfer features.

Link: https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

# **TODO Application:**

This project is a window form application with setting up what is to be done in your daily activities.

Link: https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

## **EDUCATION**

Moshood Abiola Polytechnic Abeokuta — HND (COMPUTER ENGINEERING)

August 2014 - FEBRUARY 2018

Higher National Diploma from Moshood Abiola Polytechnic Abeokuta, Nigeria.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Scrum Fundamentals 2022

EFSet - English Proficiency 2022

MTA - Into Programming in HTML & CSS 2022

Mindware - Project Management Professional 2021